What are you doing?
你在做什么?
Just taking your bags,sir.
只是在拿你的包, 先生.
Ah...So,Mr.Yamamoto?
Ah...So, Yamamoto先生?
Yes,yes.
是的, 是的.
Where is that trolley going?
那个手推车要去哪?
To the airport.
去机场.
The airport?
机场?
Well,no. The trolley's going outside to the shuttle bus.
Well, 不. 手推车去外边的往返巴士上.
The shuttle's going to the airport.
往返巴士去机场.
But I'm just checking in!
但是我刚刚登记入住呀!
That's right sir.
没错, 先生.
Do you have any bags?
你有任何包包吗?
They're going to the airport!
他们正去往机场.
What?
什么?
The porter is putting my bags on the shuttle!
行李员正把我的包放到往返巴士上!
Carl! Carl!
The bags go to Mr.Yamamoto's room!
那些包去往Yamamoto先生的房间!
What's going on?
怎么了?
-His bags are going to the airport! -My bags are going to the airport!
-他的行李正在去往机场! - 我的行李正在去往机场.
I hope you had a pleasant stay.
我希望你在这里住的愉快.
This isn't happening.
这并非(真地)在发生.
Don't worry. I'm calling.
别担心. 我在打电话.
I'm calling.
我在打电话.
What's happening now?
发生什么了现在?
Mr.Yamamoto's bags are on their way to the airport..
Yamamoto先生的行李 正在去往机场...
So?
那怎么了?
I'm trying to get them back.
我在试着把它们弄回来
Why?
为什么?
Our guest is just checking in.
咱们的客人正在登记入住.
Uh oh!
Not without my bags!
不能(入住)没有我的行李(的话)